<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>B10453K</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B00886BN6I</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-03T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Snazaroo Masks Paint Set  (8 Colors)</Title><Brand>Silly Farm</Brand><Description>Snazaroo's Halloween Mask Face Painting Kit includes the bestselling and fourth in a series, Face Painting Book of Masks by Marcella Murad.  The kit includes eight Snazaroo 2 ml face paints: Black, White, Red, Yellow, Green, Sky Blue, Orange and Bright Pink.  The Halloween mask face painting book has 25 original, fun, extraordinary yet simple unisex Batman, Unicorn, Princess and Spiderman face paint designs by Marcela Murad, an icon and pioneer in the face painting world.  Easy step-by step instructions are included and will make Halloween mask face painting a as easy as eating your Halloween candy, from a simple face paint princess crown to the advanced Spiderman face paint mask.  

Snazaroo Face Paints are hypoallergenic and the world's safest face paints, meeting US FDA, Canadian, and European standards for cosmetic safety and the only face paint with a Child Toy Safety Rating.  Snazaroo paint is non-toxic and easy to use face paint that is water-based, fragrance-free and wash off easily.  

The Halloween Mask Face Painting Kit also comes with a sturdy plastic traveling case.</Description><BulletPoint>Each 8 color Snazaroo Halloween Make Face Painting Kit will paint well over 50 faces</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>The 2ml size face paints are non-toxic, hypoallergenic and cosmetic grade  The most child friendly face paint on the market</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>The book is 56 pages and soft cover</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Kit comes in a sturdy carrying case</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Colors in kit are black, white, red, yellow, green, sky blue, orange and bright pink</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>1</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>51.140000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Silly Farm</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>BK-CPM</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>FacePaint</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>