<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F12684</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B00886JONC</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-05T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Mehron Paradise AQ Pro Face Paint Palettes (30 Colors)</Title><Brand>Mehron</Brand><Description>Mehron's Paradise Pro Palette includes 30 &quot;Basic,&quot; &quot;Pastel,&quot; and &quot;Tropical&quot; Paradise Face Paints in a laptop plastic case.  Perfect for face and body painting professionals who are on the go. It also includes extra black and white face paint.

Paradise face paints are semi-soft cake makeup co-created with Mehron by Jinny Houle, World Renowned Body Painting Artist. Paradise face paints are water activated, and because of this, the hues of the colors can be controlled by the artist.  Paradise Face Paints feature vibrant colors that dry quickly with minimal rub-off, yet are easy to blend and wash off.  Paradise AQ Makeup includes aloe and chamomile and the enriching emollients glycerin, avocado oil and cocoa butter, making them safe and gentle on skin. They have rich, vibrant, color-saturated coverage--more than ordinary makeup, yet it's water-soluble for easy soap and water removal.  

The 30 colors in the Paradise Palette 30 color are .25 ounces in size.</Description><BulletPoint>Each 30 color Paradise Makeup AQ Palette gives over 1000 applications Each 0.25 face paint color has a large surface area for use with sponge or brush</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>The colors included in the Paradise Makeup 30 Palette are Black (3), White (3), Red, Yellow, Dark Blue, Dark Green, Orange, Dark Brown, Teal, Light Green, Dark Pink, and Purple, Lagoon Blue, Beach Berry, Mango, Amazon Green, Lime, Storm Cloud, Wild Orchid, Coral, Light Pink, Light Brown, Light Blue, Violet, Gold and Silver </BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Easy to remove, just use soap and water</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Easy to blend and apply yet are resistant to smearing</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Mehron has taken face and body painting to a new level with their Paradise AQ Pro Paints</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>4.000000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>120.450000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Mehron</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>801-PAL-30C</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>face-painting-supplies</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>