<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F12600BL</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B008P0LFJM</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-05T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Mehron Liquid Face Paints - Blue BL (4.5 oz)</Title><Brand>Mehron</Brand><Description>Water based Mehron Liquid Face Paint can be used with an airbrush and is ideal for full body painting.  It is also handy for face painting crowds of faces at parties, carnivals and other events.  It can be applied with brushes, sponges or an airbrush.

Made from quality FDA approved ingredients, Mehron Liquid Makeup does not include alcohol, so it's safe and gentle on skin.  There is no water activation with liquid face paint so you can move quickly through your face paint designs. Mehron liquid paint dries quickly and has a smooth crack resistant finish.  Mehron Liquid Makeup is also a great FX makeup that can be mixed with Liquid Latex or 3D Gel. 

This 4.5 ounce bottle of Mehron Liquid Face Paint bottle does not come with an applicator brush, but is perfect for refilling smaller bottles or for really large jobs.</Description><BulletPoint>Each 4.5 ounce bottle of Mehron Blue Liquid Face Paint will work for 90-300 applications</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Mehron Liquid Face paint is water based and can be applied with a brush, sponge or an airbrush</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>The big bottle of 4.5 ounces of liquid paint is perfect for refilling small bottles or for very large jobs  It does not come with a brush</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Perfect for full body painting or for getting things moving quickly with crowds at events and carnivals</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Mehron face paints are made with FDA approve ingredients</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>0.500000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>14.930000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Mehron</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>111-BL</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>face-painting-supplies</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>