<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>B12202</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B00886C3K8</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-03T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>My Favorite 50 Walkarounds - McMullen</Title><Brand>Ickle Pickle</Brand><Description>This wonderful collection of walkaround gag ideas includes silly sketches of the props, suggested uses and constructions tips. Includes: Newspaper for Sale, Tasty Tweety, Apple for the Teacher, Quick Cash, Tax Shelter, Sponge Cake, Book Worm, Magic Top Hat, Buzz Buzz Buzz, Who is Training Who?, Box of Tricks, Bird Brain, Vanishing Foot, Danger - Baby Rattlers, Play it Again Sam, Cheesecake, Have You Seen This Clown?, Monkey Business, All Cracked Up, Popcorn Anyone?, Cow Pie, Lemon Drop, Domino's Pizza, Shave the Whales, It's Tide, Instant Credit, Say Cheese, Peanut Vendor, Pancakes, Lemonade, Moon Rock, Flower Anyone?, Remote Bug, Play Ball, Dentist, Caught in the Act, Blue Jay, Doggone, My Butterfly Collection, My Bee Collection, Money Hungry, Mirror Mirror on the Wall, How High Can you Go?, Lonely, Here Tweety, God Catcher, I'm Under A-Tack, Mouse House, Mr. Fix It, Basketball Toss. 54-page illustrated paperback.</Description><BulletPoint>54-page illustrated paperback</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>50 walk-around gags including silly sketches of props, suggested uses, and construction tips</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Essential tips for clowns and entertainers of all levels</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Walk around and entertain</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>0.250000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>14.910000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Ickle Pickle</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>1405</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>party games</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>birthday party activities</SearchTerms><ItemType>childrens-party-activities</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>