<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F14945</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B00886G8YU</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-10T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Amerikan Body Art Mini Glitter Tattoo Kits - UV/Blacklight (3 Colors)</Title><Brand>Amerikan Body Art</Brand><Description>Easy glitter mini tattoo kits from Amerikan Body Art are perfect for creating easy, quick and fun designs at face painting events. Just place a stencil down on the skin, apply the glue and glitter and there you have it--a glitter tattoo in no time at all.

Blacklight glitter is bright under normal light while fluorescing under black light.

The Glitter Tattoo kits include 3 vials of cosmetic glitter, a mini sweeper brush and an applicator for adding details plus a 3.5 ml glue applicator vial. There are 6 self-adhesive Glitter Tattoos (styles will vary) and instructions that will lead you step-by-step through the process.

There is enough glitter and glue to make over a dozen tattoos.  With care, the stencils can be used more than once.  You can purchase more stencils separately.

All Amerikan Body Arts polyester glitter is made in the USA and is safe for use on body and face.


</Description><BulletPoint>The UV/Blaklight Glitter Tattoo kit includes the colors Electric Green Electric Blue and Electric Pink  The designs include a peace sign, stars and other cool designs</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Only the highest quality ingredients in these products</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>If your child has delicate skin, do a test design on the hand</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>6 stencils and step by step instructions are included with each glitter tattoo kit</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>There is enough glitter and glue to make over a dozen designs With care, the stencils can used more than once</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>0.110000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>26.320000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Amerikan Body Art</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>MINI NIGHTCLUB</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>childrens-arts-and-crafts-kits</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>