<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F12670</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B0087288MU</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-05T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Paradise Prisma Rainbow Face Paint - Arc-En-Ceil 806-659 1.75 oz/50 gm</Title><Brand>Mehron</Brand><Description>The Mehron Paradise Arc-En-Ceil Prisma BlendSet Rainbow cakes are strips of the vibrant, semi-soft Paradise makeup. These are water based striped cakes that need just a little moisture from a sponge or brush to begin.

The brilliant, multi-color Prisma Blend split cake was designed by the Canadian face and body artist Jinny - Makeup Artiste or Genevieve Houle specifically for Paradise. Each Prisma Cake has a large surface area with equal amounts of each color so they can be applied with a sponge or large brush.

Paradise Face Paints are moist and semi-soft cakes; the colors are vibrant dry quickly with minimal smearing, yet are easy to blend and wash off.  Paradise AQ Makeup includes aloe and chamomile and the enriching emollients glycerin, avocado oil and cocoa butter, making them especially safe and gentle on skin, Paradise AQ Makeup has a richer more color-saturated coverage than ordinary makeup yet it's water-soluble for easy application and clean up.  Just use soap and water.  

The Prisma Arc-En-Ceil BlendSet includes Red, Orange, Yellow, Light Green, Light Blue and Violet and comes in a 1.75 ounce (50 gram) size.</Description><BulletPoint>Each 1.75 ounce (50 gm) Paradise Prisma Face Paint cake gives hundreds of applications</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>The Prisma Arc-En-Ceil BlendSet includes Red, Orange, Yellow, Light Green, Light Blue and Violet</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Made with aloe, chamomile and the enriching emollients glycerin, avocado oil and cocoa butter</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Easy to blend and apply yet are resistant to smearing</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Easy to remove, just use soap and water</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>0.300000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>19.560000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Mehron</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>806-AL</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>face-painting-supplies</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>