<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F13007</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B00886KCWO</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-05T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Graftobian Face Painting Stamps - Kiss</Title><Brand>Graftobian</Brand><Description>Stamp on a tattoo with Graftobian Face Paint Stamps.  These stamps are as easy as stamping the due date on a library book:  quick, simple and anyone can do it.

Graftobian Face Paint Stamps are designed for the beginner face painter or for someone who is doing a lot of faces/cheeks in a short amount of time.  They are perfect for parties and for children who would like to participate in the face painting fun.

The stamps are sturdy and made of wood, so they are easy to grip. The design area is approximately 1.25 inches by 1.875 inches and are made of deeply cut rubber so that the designs applies cleanly and distinctly, no fuzzy images.  So you have a lot of squirmy, won't-sit-still-for-a-second customers to face paint?  Stamp 'em!
</Description><BulletPoint>Clean the Graftobian Stamptoo kiss face paint stamp with mildly soapy water before storing</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Perfect for beginner face painters and for children who want to get in on the face painting action Just dip in paint and stamp</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>The Stamptoo is made of wood, making it easy to grip, the rubber design is deeply cut--no fuzzy edges</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>The design area is approximately 1.25 inches by 1.875 inches</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>0.100000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>10.960000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Graftobian</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>93101</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>childrens-art-paintbrushes</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>