<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>B12203</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B00886C4PW</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-03T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>My 50 Other Favorite Walkarounds</Title><Brand>Ickle Pickle</Brand><Description>50 more of the funniest walkaround gag ideas ever (includes silly sketches of the props, suggested uses and constructions tips). Includes: Cap-Gun, Pigs in a Blanket, Holy Bible, Hand Gun, Mouse Trap, Prescription Sunglasses, Hoop Man, Ugly Baby, No - Not More Taxes, Stockings for a Caterpillar, Bat Collection, Computer Dating, Stinky, Revenge, Busted, Smile, Friendship, Sorry - Honey, Swat Team, Car(p) Phone, Wild Ant, Drill Team, Dog Catcher, State Fly Swatter, Funny Bone, Safe Cracker, Hot Dog/Bun, Mental Floss, Ham Sandwich, Can of P's, Vegetable Truck, Pride and Joy, Heavy Weight, My CD Collection, Flowering Crab Tree, Horse-Fly, House-Fly, 3-Foot Yard Stick, Sketch Artist, 14 Carrot Necklace, Apple Computer, Bugs Bunny, Antique Lawn Mower, Baseball Bat Collection, Royal Flush, Spring Flowers, Knuckle Sandwich, Holy Mackerel, Shoe Horn, Dragon Fly. 26-page, illustrated paperback.</Description><BulletPoint>26-page illustrated paperback</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>A sequel to, &quot;My 50 Favorite Walk Arounds&quot;</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>50 Walk-around gags including silly sketches of props, suggested uses, and construction tips</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Essential tips for clowns and entertainers of all levels</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Walk around and entertain</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>0.160000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>14.820000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Ickle Pickle</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>1406</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>party games</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>birthday party activities</SearchTerms><ItemType>childrens-party-activities</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>