<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F1332</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B00885S3FS</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-07T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Snazaroo Face Paint Stencils - Celtic Knots</Title><Brand>Snazaroo</Brand><Description>Face Paint Stencils from Snazaroo make face painting easy for beginners.  A simple aid for creating professional looking face painting designs in seconds. Stamp and repeat.

These stencils can be used thousands of times because they are composed of double-ply vinyl and made with Snazaroo's proprietary lamination process. They bend and shape to fit the curves of a face. Simply hold up the face painting stencil to the skin and fill in the stencil with face paint and you are done. 

These stencils are great for parties, school events or any gathering of faces because anyone can face paint with Snazaroo stencils! 

Snazaroo Celtic Knots Face Paint Stencils are 7.25 in x 8 in and a variety of Celtic Knots -  a variety of knots and stylized graphical representations of knots. 1/pack</Description><BulletPoint>Clean with a baby wipe or wet washcloth Store flat. If cared for properly, Snazaroo stencils will last for years, even with a lot of use</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Celtic Knots Stencils include a variety of knots and stylized graphical representations of knots face painting designs</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>An easy way for beginner face painters to create fast exciting designs</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Easy to bend and fit against a face Place against skin and paint; it's easy</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Stencil sheet size is approximately 7.25 in x 7 in</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>0.030000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>24.390000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Snazaroo</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>STECELTIC</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>childrens-art-paintbrushes</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>