<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F50053</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>UPC</Type><Value>8718053826370</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2014-09-08T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Diamond FX Monster Refill - Blood Red (10 gm)</Title><Brand>Diamond FX</Brand><Description>Diamond FX Blood Red in 10 gm refill size is ideal for refilling Diamond FX 10 gm palettes. Diamond FX Essential Face Paint is a strongly pigmented water-based professional face paint. Renders lively colors and provides solid coverage that lasts all day without fading or cracking. Diamond FX maintains brightness and density even when painted over other colors. Diamond FX Essential is ideal for blending, layering or line work. Works great with less amount of water. Hypo-allergenic and non-toxic; free of perfumes.

Diamond FX is manufactured according to the EEC and FDA regulations. Tested in the Netherlands. FDA does not recommend using reds and blues (this includes greens and purples) around the eye and lip area or leaving them on the skin for long. Avoid contact with upholstery, fabric and carpets.</Description><BulletPoint>Strongly pigmented water-based face paint that is perfect for line work, blending or layering</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Provides superb, opaque coverage that lasts all day without fading or cracking</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Great for monster designs</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Easy to apply either with a sponge or a brush. Removes easily with soap and water</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Each 0.35 ounces (10 gm) Refill Container is good for 20 applications</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>0.120000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='USD'>7.190000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Diamond FX</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>R1033</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>face-painting-supplies</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>