<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F12600GO</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B00886J018</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-05T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Mehron Liquid Face Paints - Day Glow Orange GLO (4.5 oz)</Title><Brand>Mehron</Brand><Description>Water based, Day Glow Mehron Liquid Face Paint can be used with an airbrush and is ideal for full body painting. It can be applied with brushes, sponges or an airbrush machine.  The Day Glow colors are black light reactive. Note, that they glow only as their described color under a black light.  Under normal light they appear white or transparent.  They do not &quot;glow in the dark&quot; without a black light.

Made from quality FDA approved ingredients, Mehron Liquid Makeup does not include alcohol, so it's safe and gentle on skin.  There is no water activation with liquid face paint so you can move quickly through your face paint designs. Mehron liquid paint dries quickly and has a smooth crack resistant finish.  Mehron Liquid Makeup is also a great FX makeup that can be mixed with Liquid Latex or 3D Gel. 

This 4.5 ounce bottle of Mehron Liquid Face Paint bottle does not come with an applicator brush, but is perfect for refilling smaller bottles or for really large jobs.</Description><BulletPoint>Each 4.5 ounce bottle of Mehron Day Glow Orange Liquid Face Paint will work for 90-300 applications</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Glows only under black lights, not normal light Will not &quot;glow in the dark&quot; without a black light</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Can be applied with brushes, sponges or an airbrush machine</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Made only with FDA approved ingredients and is gentle on skin</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Liquid makeup needs no water activation so it's ready when you are</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>0.500000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>17.250000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Mehron</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>111-GLO</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>face-painting-supplies</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>