<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F12740</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B008NCXRSO</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-05T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Mehron Paradise Face Paints - Violet (1.4 oz)</Title><Brand>Mehron</Brand><Description>Mehron's Paradise AQ makeup is a water activated face paint that is rich in color and pipment.  This is a face paint for artists who want ease with application and creative control over color.

Paradise face paints are semi-soft cake makeup co-created with Mehron by Jinny Houle, World Renowned Body Painting Artist. Paradise face paints are water activated, and because of this, the hues of the colors can be controlled by the artist.  Paradise Face Paints feature vibrant colors that dry quickly with minimal rub-off, yet are easy to blend and wash off. Paradise Makeup includes aloe and chamomile and the enriching emollients glycerin, avocado oil and cocoa butter, making them safe and gentle on skin. They have rich, vibrant, color-saturated coverage--more than ordinary makeup, yet it's water-soluble for easy soap and water removal.  

These Paradise AQ Face Paint containers are 1.4 ounces or 40 grams.
</Description><BulletPoint>Each 1.4 ounce (40 gm) Paradise Violet Face Paint Container can be used for hundreds of applications</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Water activated semi-soft makeup that gives the face painter control over the hues of the colors</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Made with aloe, chamomile and the enriching emollients glycerin, avocado oil and cocoa butter</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Easy to blend and apply yet are resistant to smearing</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Mehron has taken face and body painting to a new level with their Paradise AQ Paints</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>1</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>15.850000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Mehron</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>800-V</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>FacePaint</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>