<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F21408</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B00A2W37GU</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-18T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>TAG Face Paint 6 Color Palette - Pearl (10g)</Title><Brand>TAG Body Art</Brand><Description>TAG Pearl Face Paint Palette comes with 6 colors (Rose, Blue, Green, Purple, Gold and Silver) in 10 gram containers. Also included is two face painting brushes: one flat and one round.

TAG Pearl Face Paint is a little softer than TAGs regular paints and contain Mica for a metallic sheen. TAG Pearl Face Paint does not contain any metal.

TAG Face Paint is very easy to blend, soft on the skin and does not crack or peel. Most of TAGs face painting colors are great for line work and lighter face painting colors show very well even when over darker colors. TAG facepaint has a wax base, so your face painting design flexes with movement instead of cracking, remains colorful and is comfortable to wear. TAG is a very soft creamy face paint and needs less water to activate than normal face paint.

TAG face paint is hypoallergenic and made with non-toxic, skin safe ingredients.

Each 6 color TAG Face Paint Palette is good for 50-200 applications.</Description><BulletPoint>Each 6 color Tag Face Paint Palette is good for 50-200 applications</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Comes with 6 colors (Rose, Blue, Green, Purple, Gold and Silver) in 10 gram containers</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>TAG Pearl Face Paint is a little softer than TAGs regular paints and contain Mica for a metallic sheen  TAG Pearl Face Paint does not contain any metal</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>TAG Face Paint is very easy to blend, soft on the skin and does not crack or peel</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>TAG face paint is hypoallergenic and made with non-toxic, skin safe ingredients</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>1</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>41.940000</MSRP><Manufacturer>TAG Body Art</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>PE6/P</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>FacePaint</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>