<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F1226</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B0057Z91MG</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-05T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Mehron Fantasy FX Liquid Face Paints - Fluorescent Lime (1 oz)</Title><Brand>Mehron</Brand><Description>Squeezable face paint in a tube: Mehron Fantasy F/X Face Paints are as easy to use as toothpaste.  They need no water activation, just squeeze and paint.

The  Fluorescent Lime Face Paint applies as &quot;yellow&quot;, and appears &quot;lime&quot; under black light.

These tubes of face paint are ideal for large events like carnivals or a large party.  If there are a lot of people to cover in one color, like a ball game, Mehron F/X tubes are ideal--just squeeze and start painting.  They also dry quickly--in less than a minute.  Once on they stay put until you wash them off with soap and water.

Mehron Face Paints are highly saturated and highly pigmented face paints of cosmetic grade.  The ingredients are FDA approved, but if skin is prone to allergies, Mehron recommends that a small patch of skin be tested with the face paint before full coverage.

Comes in a 1 ounce tube and this is good for 20  - 70 applications.</Description><BulletPoint>Each 1 ounce Mehron Fantasy FX face paint tube has 20-70 applications</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Made with high quality, cosmetic grade ingredients; they are FDA approved</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Easy to apply, easy to remove, just use soap and water</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Face Paint in a tube With Mehron F/X Face Paint Tubes, you just squeeze and paint No water activation necessary</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>1</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>8.300000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Mehron</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>FFX-GLL</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><ItemType>FacePaint</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-adult</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>