<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F10630</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B008NCX982</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-04T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Wolfe F/X Face Paint Refills - Metallix Gold 100 (5 gm)</Title><Brand>Wolfe FX</Brand><Description>Wolfe Metallic Gold Face Paint M100, one of the Wolfe Metallix line, is considered one of the best face paints on the market.  Wolfe face paints have dense pigmentation providing brilliant color, opaque coverage, and easy application.  Uniquely in the face paint world, Wolfe FX Hydrocolor makeup has a wax base so they flex with movement instead of cracking so your face paint designs stay beautiful for longer. Once applied, Wolfe face paint will not smear under normal circumstances, remain bright and colorful, and is comfortable to wear.  Wolfe Metallic Gold face paint comes in a 30, 45 or 90 gram screw-top stackable container for easy storage.</Description><BulletPoint>Each 0.18 ounces (5 gm) Wolfe Metallic Gold Face Paint Refill Container is good for 10 applications</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Metallic colors give a glistening effect to a face paint design</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Wolfe paints are one of the most popular face paints on the market--they go on smoothly and evenly and do not crack when dry</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Easy to apply and easy to remove; just use soap and water</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Dense pigmentation makes the essential colors brilliant and vibrant</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>0.120000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>10.160000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Wolfe FX</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>PA 1 M100</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>face-painting-supplies</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>