<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F10521</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>UPC</Type><Value>856408000728</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-19T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Wolfe Kids Animal Face Painting Kits</Title><Brand>Wolfe FX</Brand><Description>Wolfe Kids Animal Face Painting Kits are easy-to-use face painting makeup kits.  You can paint a variety of simple kid-friendly designs like dog, cat and fish. The Kit comes with full color photographs and a step-by-step instruction book.  This is a kit for the beginner face painter and novices who want to learn.  It is also perfect for kids to play with and paint designs on each other. Wolfe paint is the high-in-demand face paint that goes on smoothly and evenly and does not smear or crack once it is on the skin.

Wolfe makeup water based, making it easy to apply and take off-just use soap and water.  It is also safe and non-toxic which makes it perfect for kids. Wolfe face paint makeup is less likely to smear or rub off and is comfortable to wear; this makes it markedly different from typical Grease Paint.

The  Wolfe Kids Animal Face Painting Kit contains four face paint cakes (Orange, White, Gold, Light Blue), six face paint sticks (White, Blue, Yellow, Red, Green, Black), two applicator sponges, one paint brush and a detailed step by step instruction booklet with color photos.  

The Wolfe Kids Animal Face Painting Kit is perfect for play dates, play time, parties or Halloween.</Description><BulletPoint>This Wolfe Face Painting Kit is good for about 40 applications</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Full color photographs of the designs with step-by-step instructions</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Wolfe face paint goes on smoothly and easily and does not smear or crack once it has dried</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Wolfe face paint is water based, easy to apply and remove-just use soap and water</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>1</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='GBP'>14.8</MSRP><Manufacturer>Wolfe FX</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>WKL-V02b</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><ItemType>FacePaint</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-adult</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>