<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F14912</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B00886G264</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-10T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Amerikan Body Art Liquid Bling - Electric Orange (0.5 oz)</Title><Brand>Amerikan Body Art</Brand><Description>Amerikan Body Art Liquid Bling is a glitter gel that is perfect for adding accents to your face or body painting designs. Dot your design with little pieces of bling!  Liquid Bling looks just like bits of crystals.
It is so much fun to use and is a hit at face painting events.

Liquid Bling glitter gel is made from cosmetic glitter and an aloe gel without any drying agents. This keeps it from clogging up the applicator.  It dries a little slower than other glitter gel products, but applies with more ease.

The Liquid Bling bottle includes a fine-point plastic tip for fantastic control. Amerikan Body Art Liquid Bling is great for kids (and adults) who want a special finish and some ostentatious ornamentation, but need something that they can wash off at the end of the day.

Comes in an 0.5 ounce size.</Description><BulletPoint>Each 0.5 ounce bottle of Amerikan Body Art Electric Orange Liquid Bling will let you create hundreds of dots, or dozens of cheek-size designs</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Perfect for adding accents to your face or body painting designs; just dot on some bling</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Glitter gel is made from cosmetic glitter and an aloe gel</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>A hit a parties and face and body painting events</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Easy to apply and easy to remove; just use soap and water</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>0.030000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>10.470000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Amerikan Body Art</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>Liquid Bling 0.5 oz - Electric Orange</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes easily</SearchTerms><ItemType>other-arts-&amp;-crafts-glues</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>