<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F18172</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B003P980TQ</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-12T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Snazaroo Blue Cat Starter Face Painting Palettes (6 Colors)</Title><Brand>Snazaroo</Brand><Description>Snazaroo Blue Cat Starter Face Painting Palettes are ideal for face painting at parties and plays. Includes 2 ml face paints in following Snazaroo colors: White, Pale Pink, Royal Blue, Pale Blue. Also includes a sponge applicator and a brush.

The Snazaroo Starter Kit includes Snazaroo Face Paint which applies smoothly, can be easily blended and will dry in about 30 seconds to a streak-free, durable finish.  Snazaroo Face Paints are hypoallergenic and the worlds safest face paints, meeting US FDA, Canadian, and European standards for cosmetic safety and the only face paint with a Child Toy Safety Rating.  Snazaroo paint is non-toxic and easy to use face paint that is water-based, fragrance-free and wash off easily.  Snazaroo Face Paint gives brightly colored, totally opaque coverage.  </Description><BulletPoint>Each 6 color Snazaroo Starter kit will easily paint 30 full faces or hundreds of cheek designs</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Includes 2 ml face paints in following colors: White, Pale Pink, Royal Blue and Pale Blue along with a brush and a sponge applicator.</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>One of the most popular face paints in the world</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Safe face paint for children</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>0.650000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>13.750000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Snazaroo</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>PALBLUECAT</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>childrens-arts-and-crafts-kits</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>