<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>B12496</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B00886C9KM</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-04T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Ultimate Balloon Twister's Guide, Vol 2 - Echevarria</Title><Brand>Gentleman Tramp Productions</Brand><Description>Designed for beginners through advanced twisters, &quot;The Ultimate Balloon Twister's Guide&quot; has become one of the best selling books on balloon twisting in recent years. Now, 7 years after its initial release, author Eli &quot;Buster&quot; Echevarria proudly presents Volume 2 in the series. As in the first volume, beginners will be pleased with the thoroughness of the instructions. Every single step is carefully and completely explained with both text and illustrations. The more experienced twisters will be able to bypass most of the written details and follow along with only the illustrations as their guide. Volume 2 features over 115 pages of highly detailed and accurate illustrated instructions on over 60 different balloon designs, and includes step-by-step instructions of all the basic twists needed to complete each figure. Includes:  Single Balloon Designs, Multiple Balloon Designs, Holiday Balloons, Balloon Flowers, Balloon Weapons and Balloon Hats. The book also contains sections on balloon inflation techniques, balloon special effects to enhance designs, and a thorough &quot;How To&quot; guide to landing balloon twisting work in restaurants. 115-page, coil-bound, black/white paperback. Author published.</Description><BulletPoint>Over 100 pages of ballooning instructions</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Long-awaited sequel to, &quot;The Ultimate Balloon Twister's Guide&quot; by Eli &quot;Buster&quot; Echevarria</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Great for beginners and experts</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Includes over 60 different balloon designs and step-by-step instructions on twists</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>115-page, coil-bound, black/white paperback Author published</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>0.760000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>31.020000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Gentleman Tramp Productions</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>BOOK V2</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>easy balloon animals</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>twisting balloons</SearchTerms><ItemType>childrens-party-balloons</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>