<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F23672</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B010VXOXKS</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-19T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Ruby Red Face Paints - Lion Theme Kit</Title><Brand>Ruby Red Paints</Brand><Description>Ruby Red Lion Theme Kit includes three Ruby Red face paint colors to paint terrific lion face painting designs. Kit includes 3 colors - white, dark brown and ochre, each in 0.14 ounce (2 ml) size and will easily cover 30 - 40 full face applications. Kit also includes an applicator sponge.

Ruby Red face paints are long wearing, highly pigmented semi-solid cakes that can be easily activated with just a few drops of water. They apply smoothly and dry fast within 20 to 30 seconds. Ruby Red can be applied with a sponge or a brush. They provide great, opaque coverage when applied and patted with a sponge. Ruby Red face paints also work great to add fine details to your design when mixed and applied with a brush.

Ruby Red face paints are specially formulated with glycerin and other binding technologies to faciliate easy, durable application. They can be easily removed with mild soap and water. Mild baby shampoo &amp; washcloth or unscented baby wipes are other recommended ways for removal.

Gary Cole, a veteran with years of experience in the face painting industry, has introduced the Ruby Red line of face paints with the goal of providing face paints that are absolutely safe to use, especially on children. Ruby Red face paints come with a child toy safety rating. They are totally free of lanolin or any ingredients from animals and are branded as vegan. Ruby Red face paints are made in the USA and are FDA approved for use in the USA, EU, Mexico and Canada. They are made with ingredients free of paraben, nuts, gluten, latex or fragrance, which makes them hypo-allergenic and non-toxic.</Description><BulletPoint>Lion Theme kit includes 0.14 oz or 2 ml of white, ochre and dark brown face paints</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Water activated, semi-solid cake makeup with strong pigmentation</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Hypo-allergenic, non-toxic and vegan (free of any animal related product)</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Gives approximately 30-40 full face designs</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>FDA approved and made in USA</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>0.200000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>9.070000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Ruby Red Paints</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>THEMELION</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>play dress up</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>halloween masks</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><ItemType>childrens-art-paints</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience><TargetAudience>boys</TargetAudience><TargetAudience>boys</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>