<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F10681</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>GTIN</Type><Value>18537379836149</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-19T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Wolfe FX Face Paints - Metallix Silver 200 (30 gm)</Title><Brand>Wolfe FX</Brand><Description>Wolfe Metallic Silver Face Paint is Wolfe's Hydrocolor pearlescent face paint that gives a metallic sheen. Wolfe gold and silver Metallix are considered to be the best available today.

With dense pigmentation, Wolfe Hydrocolor Face Paints provide brilliant color and opaque coverage. They are uniquely easy to apply: they go on smoothly, evenly and do not crack once dry. The difference with Wolfe FX Hydrocolor makeup is a wax base so the colors flex with movement instead of cracking, so your face paint designs stay on longer and remain beautiful.  Under normal circumstances Wolfe face paint will not smear after it's been applied.  Paint your kids in the morning and they will remain bright and colorful all day long.  Wolfe paints are also comfortable to wear.

Wolfe 1.06 ounces (30 gm) face paint containers come in a screw-top stackable container for easy storage.</Description><BulletPoint>Each 1.06 ounces (30 gm) Wolfe Metallic Silver Face Paint Container is good for 50-200 applications</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Metallic colors give a glistening effect to a face paint design</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Wolfe paints go on smoothly and evenly and do not crack when dry</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Easy to apply and easy to remove; just use soap and water</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>The 30 gram size comes in a screw top container and stacks easily for easy travel and storage</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>1</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='GBP'>18.32</MSRP><Manufacturer>Wolfe FX</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>PM 1 200</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>FacePaint</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>