<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F10664</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B00886DEPG</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-05T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Wolfe FX Face Paints - Brown 020 (30 gm)</Title><Brand>Wolfe FX</Brand><Description>Wolfe's Essentials Brown Face Paint is one of Wolfe's basic face painting makeup colors.  They are &quot;essential&quot; to any palette. 

With dense pigmentation, Wolfe Hydrocolor Face Paints provide brilliant color and opaque coverage. They are uniquely easy to apply: they go on smoothly, evenly and do not crack once dry. The difference with Wolfe FX Hydrocolor makeup is a wax base so the colors flex with movement instead of cracking, so your face paint designs stay on longer and remain beautiful.  Under normal circumstances Wolfe face paint will not smear after it's been applied.  Paint your kids in the morning and they will remain bright and colorful all day long.  Wolfe paints are also comfortable to wear.

Wolfe face paint in the 30 gram containers are perfect for travel; they come in screw top containers and stack easily.</Description><BulletPoint>Each 1.06 ounces (30 gm) Wolfe Brown Face Paint Container is good for 50-200 applications</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Easy to apply and easy to remove; just use soap and water</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Wolfe paints go on smoothly and evenly and do not crack when dry</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Dense pigmentation makes the essential colors brilliant and vibrant</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Screw on lids in handy stackable containers</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>1</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>16.150000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Wolfe FX</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>PE 1 020</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>FacePaint</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>