<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>B1097</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B00KL7W6HM</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-03T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Costumes, Accessories, Props ... Made Easy - Rogers</Title><Brand>Meriwether Publishing</Brand><Description>Not a skit book, but a handy book for creating your own props! Transform common people into superheroes, movie stars, witches -- whatever illusion you want to create. Creative costuming is all in the details. In addition to a complete section of costuming, you'll learn how to accessorize your show by modifying existing items: hats and headpieces, masks, wings, jewelry and much more. The props section includes armor, thrones, dinnerware, Native American props and more. Over the years, the author has learned tons of tricks about how anyone can turn leftover clothing into fabulous costumes at a minimum expense. Little or no sewing, but it assumes you know your way to a craft or fabric store. Chapters: Introduction; Full Costumes; Jackets and Pants; Costumes for Children; Hats and Headpieces; Big Heads; Masks; Jewelery; Collars, Cuffs, Flaps and Capes; Wings; Gloves, Belts and Aprons; Feet, Shoes, and Leggings; Undergarments; Native American Props; Wands and Poles; Armour; Thrones, Crowns and Scepters; Dinnerware; Lamps; Illusions; Index. 205 pages, b/w photo/illustrated paperback.</Description><BulletPoint>205-page black and white paper back on prop creation</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Offers a complete guide to costume creation, accessories, and item modification</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Requires little to no sewing</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Inexpensive ideas</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Essential tips for clowns and entertainers of all levels</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>1.360000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>40.200000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Meriwether Publishing</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>B279</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>lawn games</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>Fun</SearchTerms><ItemType>childrens-party-activities</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>