<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>B10452K</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B00886BMI2</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-03T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Snazaroo Fairy Princess Paint Set  (8 Colors)</Title><Brand>Silly Farm</Brand><Description>Snazaroo's, The Princess Face Painting Kit includes the Face Painting Book of Fairy Princesses by Macella Murad and eight Snazaroo 2 ml face paints: Black, White, Bright Pink, Turquoise, Sparkle Orange, Sky Blue, Red and Lilac.  

This book is the third in a series tha Murad has created. The princess face painting book has 20 original,  extraordinary and beautiful, yet simple princess face painting designs. Marcela Murad is one of the pioneers in the face painting world.  The book and kit include easy step-by step instructions that will help you  make princess face painting like magic, from simple princess face paint to advanced fairy princess face painting designs.  

Snazaroo Face Paints are hypoallergenic and the world's safest face paints, meeting US FDA, Canadian, and European standards for cosmetic safety and the only face paint with a Child Toy Safety Rating.  Snazaroo paint is non-toxic and easy to use face paint that is water-based, fragrance-free and wash off easily.  

The Princess Face Painting Kit also comes with a sturdy plastic traveling case.</Description><BulletPoint>Each 8 color Snazaroo Princess Face Painting Kit will paint well over 50 faces</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Snazaroo face paints are non toxic and hypoallergenic and of high cosmetic grade</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>2ml colors include black, white, bright pink, turquoise, sparkle orange, sky blue, red and lilac</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Comes with a handy carrying case</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>The third in a series</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>1</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>51.140000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Silly Farm</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>BK-CPP</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>FacePaint</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>