<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>F14947</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B00886G9LM</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-10T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Amerikan Body Art Rainbow Glitter Tattoo Kits</Title><Brand>Amerikan Body Art</Brand><Description>Easy glitter tattoo kits from Amerikan Body Art are perfect for creating easy, quick and fun designs at face painting events. Just place a stencil down on the skin, apply the glue and glitter and there you have it--a glitter tattoo in no time at all.

The Glitter Tattoo kits include 5 vials of cosmetic glitter, a deluxe sweeper brush, alcohol swabs and an applicator for adding details plus a 10 ml glue applicator vial. There are 12 self-adhesive Glitter Tattoos (styles will vary) and instructions that will lead you step-by-step through the process.

There is enough glitter and glue to make over a 100 tattoos.  With care, the stencils can be used more than once.  You can purchase more stencils separately.

All Amerikan Body Arts polyester glitter is made in the USA and is safe for use on body and face.


</Description><BulletPoint>The Rainbow Glitter Tattoo kit includes the colors Firetruck Red, Emerald Green, Canadian Blue, Brilliant Gold and Grape Soda The designs include birds, butterflies, tribal swirls, stars and other cool designs</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Only the highest quality ingredients in these products</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>If your child has delicate skin, do a test design on the hand</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>12 stencils and step by step instructions are included with each glitter tattoo kit</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>There is enough glitter and glue to make over a 100 designs With care, the stencils can used more than once</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>0.340000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>50.750000</MSRP><Manufacturer>Amerikan Body Art</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>PARTY RAINBOW</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>halloween face painting</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>child safe</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>removes with soap and water</SearchTerms><ItemType>childrens-arts-and-crafts-kits</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>