<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><AmazonEnvelope xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="amzn-envelope.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Header><DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion><MerchantIdentifier>M_TOPSTECHNO_1216044</MerchantIdentifier></Header><MessageType>Product</MessageType><PurgeAndReplace>false</PurgeAndReplace><Message><MessageID>1</MessageID><OperationType>Update</OperationType><Product><SKU>B10510</SKU><StandardProductID><Type>ASIN</Type><Value>B00886BS72</Value></StandardProductID><ProductTaxCode>A_GEN_TAX</ProductTaxCode><LaunchDate>2015-08-03T11:00:01</LaunchDate><Condition><ConditionType>New</ConditionType></Condition><DescriptionData><Title>Brush Stroke Handbook - McNaughton</Title><Brand>F+W Media</Brand><Description>Maureen McNaughton's &quot;Brush Stroke Handbook&quot; is a face painting guide for the advanced face painter. It is a book of how brush strokes can be turned into art.  It has more than 50 unique and exciting face painting strokes and features a range of comma strokes, pressure strokes, fan strokes, teardrop strokes, scroll strokes and much more. The Brush Stroke Handbook includes step-by-step instructions and visuals for working with both round and flat brushes so you get the most out of your face painting brushes and strokes. You will also learn how to load multiple face paint colors on one brush, cotton swab or sponge for stunning effects and depth. The practiced face painter will be shown how to use the techniques presented in &quot;Brush Stroke Handbook&quot; to create fabulous flowers, butterflies, dragon wings, snake scales.  The advanced face painter will also learn abstract designs and more. This comprehensive face painting guide includes: quick-reference photos; step-by-step face painting stroke instructions; easy-to-follow worksheets for combining strokes.  There is also a section on how to avoid common mistakes and how to fix them. Full Size, Paperback, 144 Pages.</Description><BulletPoint>144 pages of great and unique brush strokes for the advanced face painter</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Enhance and improve your designs and business</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Easy to follow worksheets included and step-by-step instructions</BulletPoint><BulletPoint>Full Size, Paperback, 144 Pages</BulletPoint><ShippingWeight unitOfMeasure='LB'>1.390000</ShippingWeight><MSRP currency='CAD'>52.770000</MSRP><Manufacturer>F+W Media</Manufacturer><MfrPartNumber>9781440323935</MfrPartNumber><SearchTerms>easy face painting instructions</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>fun for kids</SearchTerms><SearchTerms>water based makeup</SearchTerms><ItemType>childrens-art-paints</ItemType><TargetAudience>unisex-children</TargetAudience></DescriptionData><ProductData><Beauty><ProductType><BeautyMisc/></ProductType></Beauty></ProductData></Product></Message></AmazonEnvelope>